Virgen master yo-yo good morning how
does me there's my computer is absurdly
slow this morning
you see it's being slow I know
okay so OBS is using a good bit Chrome
is using a good bet
what's that system library framework is
it more Chrome metadata framework what
is that and terminal is use I'm closing
crow
you know so crazy hi who's this
what about lag you want to cut the
stream for a second got my gold mater
here here we have to check to see all
right so let's get the reference manual
up
some place there's a place that I check
for this I forget exactly where it as
well below but the real thing we have to
do today is we have to use a timer if
you can't just disable interrupts like a
savage right here we go yeah so it's bit
2 of T out of our IR to bang our IR and
and I have 18 bits here so just going to
shift that by for the whole thing's 29
we sent 11 on this 18 minus 1 pressure
you know what waiting you need that what
if I just - you're on that behavior that
looks right now I also have to send sir
bits which must be set dominant but
so what that should let us do after I
build my McDonald's with delicious guys
I'm saying one two three here we could
say something like 18,000
don't seem good crashed slope
hello crash happened yeah this panda
crashed I flashed yellow high quality so
it's up here gonna fire back to one two
three and see if it works okay that
works fine just when I add extended that
it gets mad do something stupid okay
alright try something that's shorter
data
possible that the oscillators dancing it
outward when I said iron do anything
large no it worked
Wow okay actually didn't totally work so
this is wrong yeah you see so for some
reason set 9000 they're not 18000 I have
a bog oh yeah
how am i doing let's shift you look at
the ring
cool all right
it still freezes when I send large
messages now there's some chance that I
miss computed the max bits can packet
thing that might have not been for an
extended frame that's crashing because
it's exceeding that okay so let's let's
recompute this part problem we have the
start of frame the identifier whoops
let's do all the header stuff 1 plus 11
plus 1 plus 1 plus 18 plus 1 plus 2 plus
4 is 39 oh yeah that was wrong okay so
39 plus 64 plus 16 plus 1 plus 1 plus 1
plus 7 plus 3 okay so that was just a
buffer
[Music]
yeah I know the stream is still title
Sunday special alright alright and I'll
change it okay now it's mundane or me
good actually updates okay so now let's
see if my past passes the pen was crash
and gives buffer overflow but networks
[Applause]
[Music]
Monday alright cool so now the real
thing that we have to change is this
whole thing is terrible
this whole enter critical section crap
now I disabled for a long time
that's Shetty so now we're gonna need
yourselves go back
I'm trying to do it
nope nope definitely shouldn't do that
from within side
I shall endure these foots from inside
that critical section I guess doesn't
matter that much and also this is kind
of a really stupid
[Music]
okay this is shitty I just still say
Sunday splash off stupid twitch
okay so what we really want to do here
is use a timer we should figure out
which time where we're not using and
then I'm not sure if the sample at
double the rate
hope you don't I'm using there's time I
three for the fan use time or two for
the system let's see what time right we
have available in here we're gonna want
to enable that interrupt out
all right so we use to enable timer for
but apparently we don't use time' for
anymore
well let's also check the manual for the
chip those are both reference packet
boss
it is vaguely possible
no that's the reference about the
datasheet okay so it is vaguely possible
that we're gonna be able to use like the
UART or something
I doubt it but you know there's been
crazier things yeah new Tom Cruise you
know what's up that Kitty Pryde um so
contractor II we're using you know using
be 12 to be 11
I thought so we'll see you are here
marrying the wrong datasheet or is this
the wrong datasheet this is the right
datasheet
they're all these alternate functions
and this is the wrong data sheet because
the other ones down on five and six I
don't know how I got this data sheet
okay uh and which which chip is it years
ago wow this is that oh I don't want to
Excel spreadsheet
okay cool
so we actually do have a UI there you
are an Rx and you are TX theoretically
if we could figure out how to use you or
a5 I don't think we are using you are
five on panda we are I will use it for K
line then or are using you are five what
else do we have
then doubt time one show on end
I really write this well we could
actually make it like you are 5tx alert
also get we also get PB 3 which is
connected to actually the same thing or
PB for this is your at 7 so if we wanted
to use it you are we could certainly
using your wife we could also use a spy
if you like me so let's look at the you
part if there's a way to send the UART
without any stock dance you know I'm Sam
we could write some incredibly clever
yeah
oh yeah that's probably a delay in the
stream I don't know everything's lagged
bro
I mean the nice thing about using a you
are is then we wouldn't be trapped by
our basically mrs. enter episode that
bad but we have to turn off the stop
bitch support for one or two stop it's
but I want no stop it's is that possible
I want no stop it's and no start that's
one half stopped it no I want no stop it
oh yeah shower
well that stream is really laggy bros
over sample and method for clock
tolerance we love tolerance here on this
stream
you guys said you need the money thank
you thank you I love money and framing
her fractional
Lynne
no but like what I really want to do is
set the stop bit to zero can I do that
but spy Mesa that might be a better vet
so I can use pin so the Pens are
actually physically connected pb4 and PV
thirteen we could use either one of them
I can also use a light you see well so
let's think
yeah I do see my work
IG sees not gonna I decide to see how
stop it's okay I'm trying to use like an
eye to see peripheral two-bit bank and I
to say I don't see how that's gonna work
no no no no what's a serial audio
interface okay you see master features
start and stop generation but I never
want to stop I want to keep going I to
see bit bag stop condition but like is
that per byte is I do see like serial
per byte like that to have stopped its I
don't want stop its
sheekha's can't I just want to be able
to basically send any bits on the bus on
the bus
oh wait ciarán speeds fast speed up - so
I should be able to set any speed that
shouldn't be a problem
no stop generation this might be doable
that igc might be our hope well that's
kind of ugly and of course I tend the
clock to nowhere land no see I don't
like that well no I want you to just
keep going no stop that
oh and can I not set the speed to
anything set up - yeah if it has to be
some way to light glider but it doesn't
know real speeds
trying to start condition arbitration
see I don't want any of this stuff I
just wanted to bang bits on the bus so
complex
I believe that's that's the broad right
start condition know if this is gonna
work
let's check spa the problem is all these
things have concepts of bytes and we
don't want like look see how it has
bites like separately like that we don't
want that we want to just keep streaming
won't bite see like it has that that
gone okay I don't have high hopes for
using spy or something you are I to see
Tim three Chan one I think eidetic
memory is a scam
okay well let's use a timer anyway it's
at least better than what we have I
think we can set it as like the highest
priority interrupts so we're using Tim 1
and Tim to intimidate so we can use Tim
for we set up Tim - this is what we set
up Tim - the only place we set up some -
let me call that bear anywhere else we
call it um everything is a scam just a
lot of things are you have to always be
aware of scams avoiding scams is very
important
okay I don't know why I changed into
this those can certainly sit outside the
timer loop
yeah ma'am well rappers talk about that
all the time how they got rich and so on
you know I made a G today but yeah you
made it in a sleazy way shame broken if
we ever get over a hundred people in the
stream we're gonna debut new Tom Cruise
music new Tom Cruise music but they'll
be famous and I'll have to stop Jimmy
alright ok we want to use use primer or
I enabled arrows
thank you for subscribing I don't know
what timbre uie means well okay
so let's actually quantify how long the
timer can be disabled for if the max
bits is 200 and we're transmitting your
33.3 kilobits I should have 2 6
milliseconds yes I care yes please
subscribe please like and subscribe bye
it makes me feel good about myself
and six milliseconds is a long last time
bros long as time grows
that's true too can only watch the
things if you're a subscriber okay um
I like the idea of using the spy more
probably easier to set up there's such
nice cans I really want to use the cats
can't use the cans books we only have
three of them that's the whole reason
we're doing this that's right capitalism
that's right we love capitalism light
buzzing
hello guys I bought a whammo
so where mom so well
it has Wi-Fi it puts your lights on
Wi-Fi Marco he's in jail guys it's not
funny that's not funny
those assholes who put Martin
shkreli in jail that's a great man he
made great content he disrespect the
wu-tang clan now you know this married
life makes choices I would I would never
disrespect the wu-tang clan I know you
don't with the wu-tang clan they
told me that and I believe dope
dude we could watch who take planning on
but then I think we'd get
copyright straight a striked and
Ghostface Killah show up in my bathroom
beat out of me that's right
don't with loot a clan
yeah free shkreli so down bros I talk
cuz they're buzzing yeah guys yells you
made G today but you made it in the
sleazy way that's how I feel about IC oh
yeah sure man look I love let me tell
you look if you if you yeah I'm not even
[Music]
an n-bit calling I and Vic and Abel irq
okay so we're gonna have to enable timer
I are you
where does it list all my irq now this
okay so much irq let's see which one
were you want we want Tim for oh yeah
Tim for irq and okay that sounds good
I like twitch Tyler yes yes I like
twitch dog now I make 100 twitch dollars
twitch will pay me money and then I will
have $100 just like do I have $100 nope
see all I have now is dollar dollar and
we have a dollar over here maybe I have
$20 but I don't have $100 good did I not
show that well dollar yeah it's $20 I
have $20 but I don't have $100 browse
look you can what the hell would I
actually do with money I just like
getting money cuz like having money is
great because it means that you're rich
and being rich is a great thing not for
anybody else not for what you could do
with it
just for you you wake up in the morning
and you know that you are rich this is a
great feeling it's a great feeling is
something that people who aren't rich by
poor people will never experience unless
they become rich and that's the American
dream Lavanya he's dead
okay so we got to set up Tim for I don't
even know what this stuff is well I do
know this
so if that's my purse Cal and we need to
multiply that by speed yeah get it boy
[Music]
and wherever and I remember when April
24 illegal bus stop in there
I think we need to enable other things
like cr1 we need to enable that okay
eventually we're gonna have to go to the
reference manual figure out what these
things mean you took it for Tim's no no
here we go
general-purpose time 16-bit up/down auto
reload counter 16-bit programmable pris
interrupt DMA on the enable
in up counting mode also down counting
mode also PWM mode you can maybe do
eating stream someday I'll do it
so we enable the counter top counter and
not one pulse mode you need to enable
interrupts we need to enable interrupts
this is all complicated stuff
where's interrupts risk after compare
DMA wow that's wow we the way enable
inner who Dyer yes that's what I want I
want Dyer pass one trigger
all right well I guess
terrible
oh dude be smart
oh yeah well dad I mean we don't even
talk about that because if you're not
smart like sorry bros it gets much good
but like it's not like like the thing
about being rich is everybody can be
rich everybody who puts their mind to it
can be rich but not everybody can be
smart so that's why you don't talk about
that
probably good everything to see what
happens
speed is undeclared of course because I
forgot any yes kind of idiot names as
variables things like that whose date
we've gone dates updates what do now
nothing works
oh I don't want nothing works because I
set the thing to output I never put it
back okay
rarely do that do I use the other Tim
irqs
wash your hands like about Tim to know
that one uses Tim three in a pedal
there's no other pedal I just set the
status to zero or the internet doesn't
work
now
we didn't did twice notice only doesn't
keep anything though like that don't
make sense
no many int just slow Wow
so slow figure out why might not
understand what update this trigger
[Music]
update you know an overflow or underflow
oh so that's just when the timer
overflows okay I see so we're getting it
but not enough it's
my phone lines at the same rate Wow
it might be a thing I can compare it to
I have to like set the max value if I
can set that to speed speed I'm gonna
see for now deserve on the other timers
d ma what's a deem are you want to use a
deem are oh I think I could you know
we've seen this at CCR one
oh you know what I should do with the
arr
we just say like I gotta work
maybe I'm probably like off by one but
let's also not have this print stupidly
let's just say accept it bang gm1 so
still straight
[Music]
never give up never surrender
no with my pulses and get
dally was not out I did that right
updated our friendship before
no nothing yet so let's go it's nothing
it's just wow
that worked before I don't understand I
mean I guess it was multiplying my speed
but still
thank you thank you for subscribing to
my for our no nice weed I
got work today work I smoke weed before
work don't be it degenerate
thank you how much is literally just
worked
no now there's irq
okay so it's double tapping the irq I
should tell why this doesn't oh I mean I
guess I know why all right an exit zero
there okay well now let's at least
tapping hi okay for our let's figure out
with the ARR means they are oh god no no
no no D ma oh it's an address what are
we like I just
go to this section for more information
the up counting mode the counter counts
from zero to the auto reload counter
then restarts from zero and generates a
counter overflow yeah sure maybe maybe
work maybe I did it too fast speed oh
yeah look at speed
alright now I'm seeing on the
oscilloscope so all that up for you guys
see it
yeah alright so of course I'm sure that
hook shot is gonna be full of spam
broken right so we can definitely do
away with that and we can even check so
I have an idea that to interrupts are
actually happening okay do you know a
flag yeah they both have overflow and an
update happen oh okay so this is the
overflow interrupt and then there's the
update interrupt like right after and
that's why we're getting
so let's avoid because we hate
that's right don't be a savage
don't be a degenerate live a clean and
healthy lifestyle that's right
update interrupt enable trigger
interrupt enable trigger that's off
trigger and our flag update in our pen
yes Tim for SR and Tim SOR
ah yes also look at the high quality oh
yeah look at that square wave that's a
square wave gross look at that square Oh
beautiful I should know how to use this
oscilloscope measure
I miss my oldest let's go should I just
go get it
frequency 16.1 kill ours I think that
might be exactly what I want so you
actually want the freedom to be thirty
three point three so sixteen point one
times two thirty two point two scam
speed - one huh that'll increase the
speed so our frequency that we expect
sixteen point six five oh yeah that's
better
okay can be fixed
[Music]
okay that's good we set up the timer and
then we'll the interrupt now well we can
disable the wait for bus silent for now
we'll say something like oh minus one
[Music]
this over here Savage
okay let's try that so now we're sending
it quality on the timer
what quality how it works
damn bros my life is just so easy
first try works be smart and be
rich hope you had a great weekend though
you must be busy ramping up the business
but didn't want this to fall through the
cracks still would love to speak why the
do I want to talk to you do you
know things I like people who know
things okay now it's being sent on it
interrupts so that's actually much
improved okay now let's put this other
logic here this logic above set depends
if you have input if R equals zero and
last one
we could use last sending land we
shouldn't say that we should say GM
Lance and he's unfortunately you're all
in the stupid global namespace
there's a typo no put H's all the time
actually and it's actually right
actually you're right should be I in 170
that's right so we don't use last
anymore if I'm sending greater than end
packets stuffs Shamblin sending minus
one equals one very simple one last time
we should also set the priority of that
inter I'm really high I don't know if it
matters but cool
keep broke no I know I'm actually
hanging on the send anymore there's
actually hang on the Sunday all right no
even be getting dropped cyclone
so wait there is something else we want
to do we want to add the styloid couch
[Music]
that's an hour that will wait for the
bus before we there's all sorts of like
weird race conditions in the stilt oh we
can't actually send if one of them is
sending we can fix this a little bit
okay cool that's good
so waits for the moss to be silent no
gtasa is crap
if camel and send max not equal to -1
return
I want to set this in ARP is the highest
priority tail we can look for the unfit
command to do that cool
get it bros get a lot of emails on
Monday and most of them are useless crap
it's quality shippers
you make here less this stuff like might
fail occasionally
we actually shouldn't do that if we're
exiting there's a slight subtle fog here
we're not even triggering a terror
condition who knows that could be like
serious bugs there we should write tests
for this who wants to write tests who
loves tests like speed as a define is
kind of stupid
all right guys so I'm just gonna commit
this and now it won't now it won't use
the interrupts well now we won't turn
off interrupts for like you know 60
milliseconds anymore wait what oh I just
got a travesty I saying that I broke the
build all right we'll go downstairs
we'll deal with that time to go to work
guys thank you for joining so they broke
the Panda
I'm very happy with us
yes we're getting an interrupt for each
bit I'm just kind of okay
it only tries to send it once it's
probably good to boss this whole stop
all this crap you could play a little
Windex clean up song again okay thank
you for joining us for this stream make
sure to LIKE and subscribe have a nice
day everybody happy Monday
yeah that's